(Leonard:)We could throw a dinner party too.
Maybe even ask everyone to get dressed up.
Sure. Just, when you say "dressed up,"
you mean nice clothes, right?
(Penny:)Not like capes and tights and crap.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)- Although...
- No.
- Howie, you okay?
- Yeah, I just couldn't sleep.
I told you you shouldn't
have espresso after dinner.
(Bernadette:)I know the little cups make you
feel big, but it's not worth it.
(Howard:)It's this stupid letter.
- Did you read it?
- No.
- You must be curious.
- Of course I'm curious.
(Howard:)I haven't seen the man
since I was a little kid.
(Howard:)And a letter shows up
on my 18th birthday.
(Howard:)What's that about?
Then why don't you read it?
(Bernadette:)Maybe he apologizes
or explains why he left.